Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.13
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Attorney General of the United States, 1988-1991; XIII.
  - Events, 7.
    - General Events
      - Gerson, Stuart, Civil Division, Swearing-in Ceremony, Washington, DC, October 30, 1989 (Box 793, Folder 15)
      - Giamatti, Bartlett, Baseball Commissioner, Washington, DC, August 3, 1989 (Box 793, Folder 16)
      - Giamatti, Bartlett, Memorial Service, New Haven, CT, October 6, 1989 (Box 793, Folder 17)
      - Giavis, Alexandra, Office of Public Affairs (OPA), Washington, DC, April 16, 1990 (Box 793, Folder 18)
      - Gleason, Rob and Jeanne, Washington, DC, February 8, 1989 (Box 793, Folder 19)
      - Glod, Stanley, Chairman of the Foreign Claims Settlement Commission (FCSC), Washington, DC, September 16, 1988 (Box 793, Folder 20)
      - Glover, John, Farewell reception, Washington, DC, March 14, 1989 (Box 793, Folder 21)
      - "Godfather III" Screening Hosted by Jack Valenti, Washington, DC, January 2, 1991 (Box 793, Folder 22)
      - Gold, Dr. Mark, Washington, DC, April 5, 1989 (Box 793, Folder 23)
      - Goldberg, Arthur, Supreme Court Memorial Service, Washington, DC, October 15, 1990 (Box 793, Folder 24)
      - Goldberg, Fred, Commissioner of the IRS, Washington, DC, April 10, 1990 (Box 793, Folder 25)
      - Goldberg, Judge Dick, Washington, DC, May 21, 1991 (Box 793, Folder 26)
      - Good Scout Award Luncheon, Pittsburgh, PA, June 21, 1990 (Box 793, Folder 27)
      - Grand Rapids Rotary Club, Grand Rapids, MI, October 18, 1990 (Box 793, Folder 28)
      - Grand Valley State University, Allendale, MI, October 18, 1990 (Box 793, Folder 29)
      - Grant, Marcia, Washington, DC, February 7, 1991 (Box 793, Folder 30)
      - Gray, Boyden, White House Counsel (Briefing on the Chain of Command), Washington, DC, June 14, 1989 (Box 793, Folder 31)
      - Greater Spokane Substance Abuse Council, Spokane, WA, March 22, 1990 (Box 793, Folder 32)
      - Gridiron Club, Washington, DC, April 1, 1989 (Box 793, Folder 33)
      - Group of Nine, General Counsels, Washington, DC, March 19, 1991 (Box 793, Folder 34)
      - Gruber, Charles, President of the International Association of Chiefs of Police (IACP), Washington, DC, May 15, 1990, June 20, 1990 (Box 793, Folder 35)
      - Gurule, Jimmy, Office of Justice Programs (OJP), Swearing-in Ceremony, Washington, DC, September 17, 1990 (Box 793, Folder 36)
      - Haass, Richard and Susan, National Security Council (NSC), Washington, DC, April 3, 1991 (Box 793, Folder 37)
      - Hahn, Robert W., Washington, DC, March 27, 1989 (Box 793, Folder 38)
      - Hall, Gordon, Chief Justice Utah Supreme Court, Washington, DC, November 4, 1988 (Box 793, Folder 39)
      - Haller, Dr. Joe, Rocco Scalzi, and Jeff Shoaf, Washington, DC, November 3, 1988 (Box 793, Folder 40)
      - Hallett, Carol, U.S. Customs Service Commissioner, Washington, DC, November 20, 1989 (Box 793, Folder 41)
      - Handy, Tom, Washington, DC, May 20, 1991 (Box 793, Folder 42)
      - Hankinson, Richard, Inspector General, Washington, DC, February 1, 1990 (Box 793, Folder 43)
      - Hankinson, Richard, Swearing-in Ceremony, Washington, DC, July 31, 1990 (Box 793, Folder 44)
      - Harris, Dick and DeeDee, Washington, DC, November 16, 1989 (Box 793, Folder 45)
      - Hart, Kitty Carlisle, undated (Box 793, Folder 46)
      - Hart, Rosemary, Office of Legal Counsel (OLC), Washington, DC, June 27, 1991 (Box 793, Folder 47)
      - Harvard Political Review Interview, Washington, DC, October 18, 1988 (Box 793, Folder 48)
      - Hauberg, Robert, Criminal Division, Washington, DC, April 26, 1991 (Box 793, Folder 49)
      - Hayden, Mike, Governor of Kansas, Washington, DC, May 14, 1990 (Box 793, Folder 50)
      - Hayes, Lacy and Debra, Courtesy Call, Washington, DC, April 30, 1991 (Box 793, Folder 51)
      - Head, Joe and Louise, undated (Box 793, Folder 52)
      - Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society, Meeting with Phil Saperia, Washington, DC, January 25, 1989 (Box 793, Folder 53)
      - Heifetz, Daniel, Washington, DC, October 6, 1990 (Box 793, Folder 54)
      - Henderson, Doug, Washington, DC, November 3, 1988 (Box 793, Folder 55)
      - Henry, Chet, Washington, DC, September 13, 1989 (Box 793, Folder 56)
      - Heritage Foundation, Address on the "Rule of Law," Washington, DC, July 10, 1990 (Box 793, Folder 57)
      - Heritage Foundation, Associates, Washington, DC, October 11, 1989 (Box 793, Folder 58)
      - Heritage Foundation, Executive Officers Meeting, Washington, DC, July 16, 1989 (Box 793, Folder 59)
      - Hermeoza, Yliana, Former Student of the John F. Kennedy School of Government at Harvard University (KSG), Washington, DC, February 5, 1990 (Box 793, Folder 60)
      - Heroin Conference, DEA, Arlington, VA, January 10, 1990 (Box 793, Folder 61)
      - Heymann, Phil, Harvard Law Professor, Washington, DC, November 18, 1988 (Box 794, Folder 1)
      - Higgins, Stephen and Dan Harnett, Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, and Firearms (ATF), Washington, DC, November 3, 1988 (Box 794, Folder 2)
      - Hillman, Elsie, Washington, DC, February 13, 1989 (Box 794, Folder 3)
      - Hillsborough County Bar Association, Tampa, FL, November 8, 1990 (Box 794, Folder 4)
      - Hispanic American Police Command Officers Association, Washington, DC, March 30, 1989 (Box 794, Folder 5)
      - Hispanic Heritage Month, DOJ Observance, Washington, DC, September 20, 1989 (Box 794, Folder 6)
      - Hispanic National Bar Association, Washington, DC, July 9, 1990 (Box 794, Folder 7)
      - Hodel, Donald, Secretary of the Interior, September 7, 1988 (Box 794, Folder 8)
      - Hodsoll, Frank, Office of Management and Budget (OMB), CFO Legislation, Washington, DC, February 15, 1991 (Box 794, Folder 9)
      - Hoeveler, Jinny and Ann Thornburgh, July 18, 1990 (Box 794, Folder 10)
      - Holiday, Ede, White House Cabinet Secretary, Washington, DC, July 5, 1990 (Box 794, Folder 11)
      - Hoover Institution, Washington, DC, February 6, 1991 (Box 794, Folder 12)
      - Horatio Alger Awards Dinner, Washington, DC, May 18, 1990 (Box 794, Folder 13)
      - Houston Bank Fraud Conference, Houston, TX, June 13, 1989 (Box 794, Folder 14)
      - Houston Lawyers Association, Houston, TX, June 13, 1989 (Box 794, Folder 15)
      - Howard, John, Deputy Attorney General of the United States (DAG), Farewell reception, Washington, DC, July 12, 1990 (Box 794, Folder 16)
      - Hubbard, Alan, Executive Director, Council on Competitiveness, Washington, DC, July 19, 1990 (Box 794, Folder 17)
      - Hughes, Richard, Washington, DC, February 2, 1990 (Box 794, Folder 18)
      - Humphreville, John D., Washington, DC, October 11, 1990 (Box 794, Folder 19)
      - Hunt, Adriana, Memorial Service, Washington, DC, May 18, 1991 (Box 794, Folder 20)
      - Hunt, Guy, Governor of Alabama, Montgomery, AL, May 2, 1991 (Box 794, Folder 21)
      - ICITAP (International Criminal Investigative Training Assistance Program) Briefing, Washington, DC, May 25, 1990 (Box 794, Folder 22)
      - Illinois Federal Drug Grant Announcement, Chicago, IL, February 7, 1990 (Box 794, Folder 23)
      - Illinois State's Attorneys Association Luncheon, Chicago, IL, December 19, 1990 (Box 794, Folder 24)
      - Immigration Bill, White House Signing Ceremony, Washington, DC, November 29, 1990 (Box 794, Folder 25)
      - Inauguration Events, Washington, DC, January 22, 1989 (Box 794, Folder 26-27)
      - Inspector General Management Conference, DOJ, Washington, DC, July 11, 1990 (Box 794, Folder 28)
      - Institute of Politics, Cambridge, MA, December 11, 1988 (Box 794, Folder 29)
      - INS (Immigration and Naturalization Service), Brown Bag Lunch, Washington, DC, March 14, 1990 (Box 794, Folder 30)
      - INS, San Diego Sector Border Patrol, San Ysidro, CA, October 24, 1988 (Box 794, Folder 31)
      - Interagency Bank Fraud Working Group, Washington, DC, December 15, 1988 (Box 794, Folder 32)
      - International Association of Chiefs of Police Conference, Portland, OR, October 11, 1988 (Box 794, Folder 33)
      - International Association of Chiefs of Police Executive Board, Washington, DC, April 19, 1991 (Box 794, Folder 34)
      - International Association of Chiefs of Police Conference, Tulsa, OK, October 8, 1990 (Box 794, Folder 35)
      - International Club #1, Washington, DC, September 26, 1990 (Box 794, Folder 36)
      - International Drug Enforcement Conference VII, Miami, FL, April 26, 1989 (Box 794, Folder 37)
      - International Symposium on Money Laundering, Miami, FL, October 27, 1989 (Box 794, Folder 38)
      - INTERPOL, undated (Box 794, Folder 39)
      - Iowa Drug Conference, Des Moines, IA, February 8, 1990 (Box 794, Folder 40)
      - Iran Contra Subpoena, Washington, DC, September 12, 1988 (Box 794, Folder 41)
      - Jackson, Michael, September 13, 1990 (Box 794, Folder 42)
      - Jackson, Reverend Jesse, August 21, 1990, August 5, 1991 (Box 794, Folder 43)
      - Jackson, William, December 15, 1988 (Box 794, Folder 44)
      - Japanese-American Redress Check Presentation, Washington, DC, October 9, 1990 (Box 795, Folder 1)
      - JFK School of Government Forum on Three Mile Island (TMI), Cambridge, MA, March 23, 1989 (Box 795, Folder 2)
      - JFK School of Government Reception in Honor of the Attorney General, Cambridge, MA, December 12, 1988 (Box 795, Folder 3)
      - JFK School of Government's Washington Alumni Association Reception in honor of Graham Allison, Washington, DC, May 4, 1989 (Box 795, Folder 4)
      - Jordan, Vernon, Washington, DC, February 22, 1990 (Box 795, Folder 5)
      - Meeting of the Federal Judicial Selections Committee, Washington, DC, September 20, 1988 (Box 795, Folder 6)
      - Judicial Conference, Washington, DC, April 29, 1991 (Box 795, Folder 7-8)
      - Judicial Conference, Executive Committee, Washington, DC, 1989 (Box 795, Folder 9)
      - Judicial Selection Process, Washington, DC, September 14, 1988 (Box 795, Folder 10)
      - Justice Department Executives, Washington, DC, June 22, 1989 (Box 795, Folder 11)
      - Justice Management Division, Brown Bag Lunch, Washington, DC, February 2, 1990, February 12, 1991 (Box 795, Folder 12)
      - Justice Management Division, Facilities 2000 Briefing, Washington, DC, January 2, 1990 (Box 795, Folder 13)
      - Kamenar, Paul, Washington Legal Foundation, Washington, DC, May 22, 1989 (Box 795, Folder 14)
      - Kansas Bar Association, Wichita, KS, June 6, 1991 (Box 795, Folder 15)
      - Kansas City Crime Commission, Kansas City, MO, October 25, 1990 (Box 795, Folder 16)
      - Kaufman, Ronald, Deputy Assistant to the President for Presidential Personnel, Washington, DC, March 29, 1989 (Box 795, Folder 17)
      - Kearns, David, Dinner hosted by K. Graham, Washington, DC, June 17, 1991 (Box 795, Folder 18)
      - Keating, Frank and Cathy McLean, VA, September 30, 1988 (Box 795, Folder 19)
      - Kemp, Evan, Washington, DC, February 14, 1989 (Box 795, Folder 20)
      - Kemp, Jack, Secretary of the HUD (Department of Housing and Urban Development), March 17, 1989 (Box 795, Folder 21)
      - Kennedy Center, Red Army Song and Dance Ensemble, Washington, DC, September 29, 1990 (Box 795, Folder 22)
      - Kennedy School, Dean's Weekend, Cambridge, MA, May 17, 1991 (Box 795, Folder 23)
      - Kennedy School, Summer Interns, Washington, DC, July 5, 1990 (Box 795, Folder 24)
      - Kennedy, Robert F., Journalism Awards, McLean, VA, May 14, 1990 (Box 795, Folder 25)
      - King, Dr. Martin Luther, Washington, DC, January 8, 1990 (Box 795, Folder 26)
      - King, Rodney Glenn (LAPD Incident), Meeting with President Bush, Washington, DC, March 21, 1991 (Box 795, Folder 27)
      - King, Tom, Karen Smith, and Dave Burroughs, Washington, DC, August 18, 1989 (Box 795, Folder 28)
      - Kirk, Dr. Jerry, Chairman, Religious Alliance Against Pornography, Washington, DC, October 27, 1988 (Box 795, Folder 29)
      - Kirkpatrick, Jaime, Washington, DC, December 21, 1988 (Box 795, Folder 30)
      - Kirkpatrick and Lockhart Lunch, Pittsburgh, PA, November 7, 1989 (Box 795, Folder 31)
      - Kmiec, Doug, Washington, DC, June 20, 1989 (Box 795, Folder 32)
      - Koop, Dr. C. Everett, Surgeon General, undated (Box 795, Folder 33)
      - Korten, Pat, Farewell party, Washington, DC, October 4, 1988 (Box 795, Folder 34)
      - Kourakos, Stella, DOJ Employee, Washington, DC, October 19, 1988 (Box 795, Folder 35)
      - Lancaster, Pennsylvania Trip with President Bush to Lancaster, PA, March 22, 1989 (Box 795, Folder 36)
      - Larson, Tom, Swearing-in Ceremony, Federal Highway Administrator, Washington, DC, March 20, 1991 (Box 795, Folder 37)
      - Law Enforcement Coordinating Committee Conference (LECC), Mississippi, May 3, 1991 (Box 795, Folder 38)
      - Law Enforcement Coordinating Committee Conference (LECC), Conference, Atlanta, GA, June 19, 1991 (Box 795, Folder 39)
      - Law Enforcement Component Head Meeting, Washington, DC, October 19, 1990 (Box 795, Folder 40)
      - Law Enforcement Steering Committee Meeting, Washington, DC, October 26, 1989 (Box 796, Folder 1)
      - Lawn, Jack, Administrator of DEA, Washington, DC, September 9, 1988 (Box 796, Folder 2)
      - Lawn, Jack, Farewell Reception and Dinner, Washington, DC, March 20, 1990 (Box 796, Folder 3)
      - Lawyers Club of Atlanta, Atlanta, GA, November 20, 1990 (Box 796, Folder 4)
      - Lawyers Committee for Civil Rights Under the Law, Washington, DC, April 19, 1989 (Box 796, Folder 5)
      - Lay, Donald, Chief Judge of the 8th Circuit, Washington, DC, February 20, 1990 (Box 796, Folder 6)
      - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights, January 11, 1989 (Box 796, Folder 7)
      - League of United Latin American Citizens and Latino Issues Forum, Washington, DC, January 13, 1989 (Box 796, Folder 8)
      - Legal Advocates in Education, DOJ, Washington, DC, March 22, 1991 (Box 796, Folder 9)
      - Lester, Martha, Southwestern Pennsylvania Industrial Resource Centers, November 1988 (Box 796, Folder 10)
      - Letelier Case, Meeting with Jerry Shestak, Washington, DC, July 16, 1991 (Box 796, Folder 11)
      - Levin, Daniel, Washington, DC, July 26, 1990 (Box 796, Folder 12)
      - Levinson, John, undated (Box 796, Folder 13)
      - Lewis, Drew, CEO of Union Pacific Corporation, Washington, DC, December 17, 1990 (Box 796, Folder 14)
      - Lincoln Club of Orange County, Irvine, CA, June 20, 1990 (Box 796, Folder 15)
      - Lincoln Legal Foundation, Chicago, IL, August 20, 1990 (Box 796, Folder 16)
      - Linn County Bar Association Address, Cedar Rapids, IA, February 8, 1990 (Box 796, Folder 17)
      - Litigation Division Heads, Washington, DC, July 31, 1991 (Box 796, Folder 18)
      - Loeper, Joe, Washington, DC, March 20, 1991 (Box 796, Folder 19)
      - Los Angeles Gangs Briefing, Los Angeles, CA, April 24, 1989 (Box 796, Folder 20)
      - Los Angeles Mayor's Alliance for a Drug-Free Community, Washington, DC, September 25, 1990 (Box 796, Folder 21)
      - Los Angeles World Affairs Council, Luncheon Address, Los Angeles, CA, April 24, 1989 (Box 796, Folder 22)
      - Lowery, Joseph, Southern Christian Leadership Conference, Washington, DC, July 24, 1989 (Box 796, Folder 23)
      - Lucas, Bill, Office of Liaison Services (OLS), Washington, DC, July 13, 1989 (Box 796, Folder 24)
      - Lucas, Bill, Office of Liaison Services (OLS), Outreach Program, Washington, DC, January 3, 1990 (Box 796, Folder 25)
      - Luce, Tom, Dallas, TX, April 23, 1990 (Box 796, Folder 26)
      - Lungren, Dan (former CA Congressman), Washington, DC, January 18, 1990, January 24, 1991 (Box 796, Folder 27)
      - Luttig, Mike, Office of Legal Counsel (OLC), Washington, DC, January 25, 1991 (Box 796, Folder 28)
      - Macdonald, Dr. Ian, Deputy Assistant to the President for Drug Abuse Policy, Washington, DC, September 19, 1988 (Box 796, Folder 29)
      - Mackey, John, Office of Liaison Services (OLA), Washington, DC, February 2, 1990 (Box 796, Folder 30)
      - Madigan, Ed, Secretary of Agriculture for the Department of Agriculture, Washington, DC, March 12, 1991 (Box 796, Folder 31)
      - Major City Chiefs/NEI Training Conference, Lake of the Ozarks, MO, May 30, 1990 (Box 796, Folder 32)
      - Mahoney, Maureen, Deputy Solicitor General, Washington, DC, July 2, 1991 (Box 796, Folder 33)
      - Maltby, Sarah, Office of Public Affairs (OPA), Washington, DC, April 9, 1991 (Box 796, Folder 34)
      - Mandela, Nelson, Address to Congress, Washington, DC, June 26, 1990 (Box 796, Folder 35)
      - Marcos Indictment, Meeting with President Reagan, Washington, DC, December 15, 1988 (Box 796, Folder 36)
      - Marcy, Kristine, Deputy Attorney General of the United States (DAG), Washington, DC, March 8, 1991 (Box 796, Folder 37)
      - Marks, Congressman Marc and Governor Ray Shafer, Washington, DC, January 5, 1989 (Box 796, Folder 38)
      - Martin, Lynn, Secretary of Labor, Washington, DC, February 22, 1991 (Box 796, Folder 39)
      - Martinez, Robert, Director of the Office of National Drug Control Policy (ONDCP), Washington, DC, January 9, 1991 (Box 796, Folder 40)
      - Martinez, Robert, Governor of Florida, Washington, DC, January 26, 1989 (Box 796, Folder 41)
      - Martoche, Salvator, Assistant Secretary of the Treasury for Enforcement, Washington, DC, October 13, 1988 (Box 796, Folder 42)
      - Marzulla, Roger, Lands Division, Washington, DC, January 18, 1989 (Box 796, Folder 43)
      - Mecham, Ralph, Director, Administrative Office for U.S. Courts, Washington, DC, July 25, 1989 (Box 796, Folder 44)
      - Medal of Freedom Award Presentation to Generals Powell and Schwarzkopf, Washington, DC, July 3, 1991 (Box 796, Folder 45)
      - Meese Portrait Unveiling, Washington, DC, July 25, 1991 (Box 796, Folder 46)
      - Mehan, Tom, Washington, DC, September 10, 1990 (Box 796, Folder 47)
      - Memphis Neighborhood Watch Awards Breakfast, Memphis, TN, March 10, 1990 (Box 796, Folder 48)
      - Mercer, Bill, Washington, DC, May 19, 1989 (Box 796, Folder 49)
      - Merchants and Manufacturers Association, Universal City, CA, June 27, 1990 (Box 796, Folder 50)
      - Merrill Lynch Board of Directors, Washington, DC, December 4, 1989 (Box 796, Folder 51)
      - Merrill, Tom, Deputy Solicitor General, Farewell Reception, Washington, DC, May 18, 1990 (Box 796, Folder 52)
      - Mid-America Committee, Chicago, IL, June 27, 1989 (Box 796, Folder 53)
      - Midby-Byron Center for Judicial Education, Reno, NV, November 9, 1990 (Box 796, Folder 54)
      - Millbank Memorial Fund, Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA) Reception, Washington, DC, July 24, 1991 (Box 796, Folder 55)
      - Miller, Bob, Governor of Nevada, Washington, DC, February 26, 1991 (Box 797, Folder 1)
      - Miller, Loye, Office of Legislative Affairs (OLA), Farewell Party, Washington, DC, May 2, 1989 (Box 797, Folder 2)
      - Montgomery County (Alabama) Bar Association Law Day Luncheon, Montgomery, AL, May 2, 1991 (Box 797, Folder 3)
      - Moore, Mike, United States Marshals Service (USMS), Swearing-in Ceremony, Washington, DC, December 6, 1989 (Box 797, Folder 4)
      - Morales, Dan, Attorney General of Texas, Washington, DC, March 19, 1991 (Box 797, Folder 5)
      - Morris, Joseph, Office of Legislative Affairs (OLA), Washington, DC, September 16, 1988 (Box 797, Folder 6)
      - Morris, Stan, United States Marshals Service (USMS), Farewell Reception, Washington, DC, October 30, 1989 (Box 797, Folder 7)
      - Mosbacher, Robert, Secretary of Commerce (Lunch and Address to General Counsel's Office), Washington, DC, August 9, 1990 (Box 797, Folder 8)
      - Mueller, Robert (Criminal Division), Washington, DC, April 3, 1989 (Box 797, Folder 9)
      - Muller, Bob and Sandra Parrino, National Council on the Handicapped, Washington, DC, June 8, 1989 (Box 797, Folder 10)
      - Murphy, Mark (Civil Division), Washington, DC, October 23, 1990 (Box 797, Folder 11)
      - Myers, Bill, Office of the Attorney General (OAG), Washington, DC, May 24, 1989 (Box 797, Folder 12)
      - McGuigan, Pat, Farewell Reception, Washington, DC, June 18, 1990 (Box 797, Folder 13)
      - McGuigan, Pat, Lunch with Dan Casey, Washington, DC, May 30, 1990 (Box 797, Folder 14)
      - McKillip, Emily, Washington, DC, July 31, 1991 (Box 797, Folder 15)
      - McKillip, Jackie and Close-Up Students, Washington, DC, January 27, 1989 (Box 797, Folder 16)
      - McLaughlin, Ann, Secretary of Labor, Washington, DC, October 5, 1988 (Box 797, Folder 17)
      - McMunn, David and Richard Porter, Washington, DC, November 7, 1990 (Box 797, Folder 18)
      - McNary, Gene, Immigration and Naturalization Services (INS), Washington, DC, November 16, 1989 (Box 797, Folder 19)
      - McNary, Gene, INS, Texas and Miami Asylum Policy, Washington, DC, February 2, 1990 (Box 797, Folder 20)
      - NAACP (National Association for the Advancement of Colored People), Legal Defense Fund, Washington, DC, September 22, 1988 (Box 797, Folder 21)
      - NAACP, Meeting with President Bush and Benjamin Hooks, Washington, DC, January 22, 1990 (Box 797, Folder 22)
      - Nagel, Ilene, Commissioner, U.S. Sentencing Commission, Washington, DC, February 8, 1989 (Box 797, Folder 23)
      - Nashville Exchange Club, Nashville, TN, March 9, 1990 (Box 797, Folder 24)
      - Nassau County Bar Association, Uniondale, NY, May 11, 1991 (Box 797, Folder 25)
      - National Academy of Public Administration, Washington, DC, December 2, 1988 (Box 797, Folder 26)
      - National Advisory Commission on Law Enforcement, Bowsher Breakfast, undated (Box 797, Folder 27)
      - National Association of Attorneys General, Washington, DC, March 13, 1991, March 19, 1990, March 13, 1989 (Box 797, Folder 28)
      - National Association of Attorneys General, Antitrust Working Group, Washington, DC, October 3, 1989 (Box 797, Folder 29)
      - National Association of Countries, Executive Committee, Washington, DC, September 7, 1989 (Box 797, Folder 30)
      - National Association of Women's Judges, Annual Conference, Washington, DC, November 10, 1989 (Box 797, Folder 31)
      - National Conference of Christians and Jews, Humanitarian Award, Chicago, IL, August 20, 1990 (Box 797, Folder 32)
      - National Conference on Improving the Quality of Criminal History Records, Washington, DC, June 20, 1991 (Box 797, Folder 33)
      - National Conference on State and Local Drug Policy, Office of National Drug Control Policy (ONDCP), Arlington, VA, May 15, 1990 (Box 797, Folder 34)
      - National Council of Jewish Women, DOJ Session, Washington, DC, March 13, 1989 (Box 797, Folder 35)
      - National Crime Prevention Council (MCGRUFF), Washington, DC, December 7, 1989 (Box 797, Folder 36)
      - National Crime Victims Rights Ceremony, Washington, DC, April 22, 1991 (Box 797, Folder 37)
      - National Disability Employment Awareness Month, DOJ, Washington, DC, October 30, 1990 (Box 797, Folder 38)
      - National District Attorneys Association, Conference, Portland, ME, July 19, 1989 (Box 797, Folder 39)
      - National District Attorneys Association, Conference, Tucson, AZ, July 15, 1991 (Box 798, Folder 1)
      - National District Attorneys Association, Executive Committee, Washington, DC, May 20, 1991 (Box 798, Folder 2)
      - National Drug Control Strategy I, Washington, DC, September 6, 1989 (Box 798, Folder 3)
      - National Drug Control Strategy II, Washington, DC, January 25, 1990 (Box 798, Folder 4)
      - National Drug Control Strategy III, Washington, DC, January 31, 1991 (Box 798, Folder 5)
      - National Drug Intelligence Center, Washington, DC, January 16, 1991 (Box 798, Folder 6)
      - National Drug Policy Board, Washington, DC, September 26, 1988 (Box 798, Folder 7)
      - National Easter Seal Society, Baltimore, MD, November 16, 1990 (Box 798, Folder 8)